<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UNTMapRouter</string>
    <string name="placeholder">PLACEHOLDER</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="src_hint">Select a source</string>
    <string name="dest_hint">Select a destination</string>
    <string name="about_us_button">About Us</string>
    <string name="calculate_button">Calculating Route</string>
    <string name="about_title">About Our App: UNT Map Route</string>
    <string name="about_intro">
        Welcome to UNT Map Route App, a navigating system for students at UNT.
        Developed by a team of 5 students who are trying to simplify how one travels around UNT.
    </string>
    <string name="about_memberinfo">
        \tOur mission was to create an app that can serve as a tool for individuals who find UNT\'s maps, online or physical, confusing and hard to read.
        We focused on creating an easy to use experience for any student or guest visiting the campus. Whenever a student or guest wants to find a specific location
        or has trouble interpreting the overly detailed maps around campus, our app is the solution. We take existing maps and overlay them into a graph with
        popular intersections that existing students use to travel across the campus. With this graph we then use our algorithm to find the shortest path between
        two locations specified by the users. Taking the graphs solution, we translate it into a digestible and familiar output for users to follow step by step.\n\n

        \tVersion 1.0.0:\n\n
        \t-Allows users to look up locations and get a route to each.\n
        \t-Does not have GPS capability.\n
        \t-Operates only on a small section of the main university.\n
        \t-Algorithm is based off of Depth First Search.\n\n

        \tVersion 1.0.1:\n\n
        \t-Expanded Map Routes\n
        \t-Improve Algorithm used to find shortest path.\n
        \t-Improve App Layout to accommodate new map expansion.\n
        \t-Added distance and time to routes.\n\n

        \tProgrammers:\n\n
        \t\tTrung Du: Asian Wizard, enchanting users and teammates with his coding knowledge\n\n
        \t\tAndres Montoya: Pokemon Trainer, fearlessly tracks down and captures bugs before they can cause mischief and endless hours of pain.\n\n
        \t\tNathaniel Schimpf: StarWars Jedi, with magical hands craft lines of code to bring the app to life\n\n
        \t\tSain Madrigal: Coding Ninja, gathers insights and feedback to help team improve the app\n\n
        \t\tKoffi Amematekpo: Data Paladin, defends the code realm to dazzle users and bring joy to their navigation experience through accessibility and usability.\n\n

    </string>
</resources>